erm very
[Music]
a little
Mm yes, but she was sloppy in a way and
had rap quick comments about a lot
as one just va v Did you get out of here like that
you kind of laugh
I'm texting saga asking How was last time
my
uh got no reply So I'm texting again
eh and I then pondered only Hm she said
maybe that she would work So me
thinking like this She might be at work
but she still usually replies to the text messages like that
didn't want to talk so much No for him
was new and stuff for us And then so
he was kind of normal
person I had no such expectation
or this bad things or good
things just normal type etc
etc. Has Saga mentioned anything about that
and what I mean by others really
It is not a specific ethnicity
or so
eh but it's a generalization of
girls then Uh generally my first question
in this in this section was about
your parents had an opinion